mindthemunchies.com 2015-09-13

# Privacy Policy | Mind The Munchies

This privacy policy sets out how MindTheMunchies uses and protects any information that you give MindTheMunchies when you use this website.

MindTheMunchies is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

MindTheMunchies may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from June 1st 2013.

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather**

When you enter your details on mindthemunchies.com you are agreeing to receive promotional offers from mindthemunchies.com and possibly third parties based in the UK, EEA, USA or Canada. These promotional offers could be sent to you by email, in the post, by telephone or by text message. Please be aware that these countries have less stringent data security standards than those of the UK, and that by signing up on this site you are agreeing to the transfer of your information to those countries.

If you would prefer not to receive promotions in the future, you can unsubscribe at any time.

Mind The Munchies reserves the right to transfer or sell your personal information to companies who are affiliated with Mind The Munchies; this is at our sole discretion. If Mind The Munchies changes ownership through a merger or sale, it reserves the right to transfer or assign the right to use your Personal Information collected from mindthemunchies.com.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, **** we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.mindthemunchies.com.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.mindthemunchies.com

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Users may opt out of the Media.net cookie by visiting the Media.net privacy policy at the following URL – [http://www.media.net/adchoices](http://www.media.net/adchoices)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our current advertising partners include:

_**Google Adsense**_

_**Media.net**_

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.mindthemunchies.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.mindthemunchies.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.mindthemunchies.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at mindthemunchies [at] gmail [dot] com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email mindthemunchies [at] gmail [dot] com.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
